http://www.boson.com/privacypolicy

Certifications
Cisco
Associate (CCNA)
Professional (CCNP)
CCNP Data Center
CCNP Enterprise
CCNP Security
Expert (CCIE)
Cisco
Associate (CCNA)
Professional (CCNP)
Expert (CCIE)
Cisco
Associate (CCNA)
CCNA Bootcamp
Cyber Ops
DevNet Associate, 200-901 DEVASC
Professional (CCNP)
300-920 DEVWBX
Expert (CCIE)
Cisco
Associate (CCNA)
Professional (CCNP)
Expert (CCIE)
Search
Privacy Policy Statements: Boson.com™ | Boson Software™ ProductsBoson.com™ Privacy Policy Statement This Privacy Policy describes how personal information is collected and used at this site (Boson.com™). Please read this privacy policy before using this site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and you will have the ability to opt out at any time.
The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for the Web site of www.boson.com and our brands. Collection of Information When you visit this site, we collect non-personal information such as information about your web browser, referrer URL and time zone. We also collect information regarding customer activities on our site in an effort to better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services and advertising.We collect personal information and Boson product user data that is voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is used to fulfill your specific request (for example, to fulfill an order or to add you to one of our mailing lists). Use of Information Any of the information that we collect may be used to: Personalize your experience. Improve our Web site. Improve customer service. Process transactions. Send periodic e-mails about product information and updates, company news, service information, etc. Administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site features. Cookies and Tracking Technology This site uses cookie and tracking technology to gather session information. Cookies help to customize the site for visitors. Personal information is not collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Sharing of Information We may share your information with third parties to help us with the Use of Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the site. We may share information with government agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may share information when (1) required by law, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions, or (3) investigating fraud that has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. Your RightsIf at any time you would like to access, update or delete your personal information, you can update your account information and preferences at www.boson.com/account or by sending an e-mail to support@boson.com. Boson Software™ Products Privacy PolicyThis Product Privacy Policy describes how information is collected in the software when a Boson software product is installed and/or activated. Please read this privacy policy before using the software. By using the software, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and you will have the ability to opt out at any time. The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for Boson software products only Collection of InformationWe collect user information, such as labs or exams attempted, labs or exams completed, search terms, etc., that is voluntarily submitted by our users. This information is used to fulfill specific requests (for example, to report the successful completion of a lab or exam on the user’s dashboard) unless you give us permission to use it in another manner. Use of InformationAny of the information that we collect may be used to:Personalize your experience.Improve our software.Improve customer service.Send periodic notifications about product information and updates, company news, service information, etc.Sharing of InformationWe may share your information with third parties to help us with the Use of Information, as described above. In addition, where an employer or training provider is the purchaser, user data may be shared with the user’s knowledge. We may share information with government agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may share information when (1) required by law, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions, or (3) investigating fraud that has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.Opting Out of My Boson NetSim ExperienceIf at any time you would like to opt out of this software’s collection of information, you may do so by going to Edit > Preferences, and then clearing the "Improve your experience by sharing usage data of the NetSim software" check box under Privacy Settings.Opting Out of My Boson Exam Environment (BEE) ExperienceIf at any time you would like to opt out of this software’s collection of information, you may do so by going to the Application Settings > Privacy, and then clearing the "Improve your experience by sharing usage data of this software" check box.Contact Information If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below: By e-mail:
support@boson.com
By phone:
877-333-3926 (toll free) or 813-925-0700
By mail:
25 Century Blvd., Ste. 500
Nashville, TN 37214-3679
We reserve the right to make changes to these policies. Any changes to the policies will be posted.PRIVACY.20180525
Boson specializes in providing robust examination preparation materials used by individuals, businesses, academic institutions and government entities around the world.
Company
About Us
Boson Blog
Careers
Trademarks
Products
NetSim
ExSim-Max
© 2020 Boson Holdings, LLC. All rights reserved.
